- 有隐喻的作用 - 我都知道
- it's metaphor. - i know.
我只是想把这一幕推迟到下周而已
I know, but we can just- we can do it next week
- 这不会影响什么的 - 不行 格雷格
- it's not a big deal. - no, i can't, greg!
对不起 我不会答应你的
It's impossible. i'm sorry.
汤米
Tommy?
我没有给其他任何人特殊待遇
I can't give you special treatment, greg.
就连你也不例外 格雷格
When i can't give special treatment to everybody.
在这里的每个人 都很努力工作
Everybody here working hard.
我只求你这一次 以朋友的名义
One favor. i'm just asking for a tiny favor as a friend.
求我 求我 你总是在求我
Favor, favor, favor. you always ask favor.
这只是一件小事啊
This is one tiny thing, that's it!
我带你来洛杉矶 给你地方住
I take you to los angeles, give you place to stay.
我为你写剧本
I write you this part.
我拍这部电影就是为了你 格雷格
I do this whole movie for you, greg?
兄弟 你拍这部电影不是为了我
You did it for me? come on, man.
- 为了我们 我们是一起的 对吧 - 对 我知道
- for us? we do it together, right? - okay, i know.
是的 这是属于我们的电影 这一点不会改变
Yes, it's our movie. this doesn't change that.
别背叛我 格雷格
Don't betray me, greg.
我不会背叛你的
I'm not betraying you.